export const quiz = {
    questions: [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Who is Jordan\'s favorite anime man?',
        answers: ['Toru Oikawa', 'Toji Fushiguro', 'Meguru Bachira', 'Kyo Sohma'],
        correctAnswer: 'Toji Fushiguro',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'What is Jordan\'s favorite Squishmallow animal?',
        answers: ['Cow', 'Food', 'Dragon', 'Cat'],
        correctAnswer: 'Dragon',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'What is Jordan NOT afraid of?',
        answers: ['Big Foot', 'Sharks', 'Dry Feet/Skin', 'Spiders'],
        correctAnswer: 'Spiders',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'What is Jordan\'s shoe size?',
        answers: ['6', '6.5', '7', '7.5'],
        correctAnswer: '7.5',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'What color is Jordan\'s hair? (Controversial)',
        answers: ['Dirty Blonde', 'Light Brown', 'Dark Brown', 'Red'],
        correctAnswer: 'Dirty Blonde',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question: 'What color are Jordan\'s eyes? (Also Controversial)',
        answers: ['Brown', 'Hazel', 'Green', 'Blue'],
        correctAnswer: 'Green',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'What is Jordan\'s undergraduate degree?',
        answers: ['Biology', 'Environmental Science', 'Microbiology', 'Biochemistry'],
        correctAnswer: 'Microbiology',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'What class did Jordan get a B in during undergrad?',
        answers: ['Industrial Microbiology', 'Organic Chemistry', 'Biochemistry', 'Chemistry 1'],
        correctAnswer: 'Chemistry 1',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which Pokemon would Jordan smash?',
        answers: ['Ditto', 'Lucario', 'Vaporeon', 'Absol'],
        correctAnswer: 'Lucario',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question: 'How many Squishmallows are in Jordan\'s room right now?',
        answers: ['15', '17', '21', '23'],
        correctAnswer: '17',
      },
      {
        id: 11,
        question: 'What is Jordan\'s favorite Studio Ghibli movie?',
        answers: ['Kiki\'s Delivery Service', 'Spirited Away', 'Howl\'s Moving Castle', 'Princess Mononoke'],
        correctAnswer: 'Princess Mononoke',
      },
      {
        id: 12,
        question: 'Which one of the following is a weird thing Jordan cannot remember?',
        answers: ['Left vs Right', '12pm vs 12am', 'Lay down vs Lie down', 'Its vs It\'s'],
        correctAnswer: 'Left vs Right',
      },
      {
        id: 13,
        question: 'Which is NOT one of Jordan\'s favorite movies?',
        answers: ['The Martian', 'Marcel the Shell', 'Hidden Figures', 'We\'re The Millers'],
        correctAnswer: 'Marcel the Shell',
      },
      {
        id: 14,
        question: 'What professor is Jordan working for at Clemson?',
        answers: ['Dr. Cao', 'Dr. Weinbrenner', 'Dr. Abercrombie', 'Dr. Kurtz'],
        correctAnswer: 'Dr. Kurtz',
      },
      {
        id: 15,
        question: 'Who is Jordan\'s best boyfriend?',
        answers: ['Jackson', 'Jackson', 'Jackson', 'Jackson'],
        correctAnswer: 'Jackson',
      },
    ],
  };
  
  export default quiz;